SHANNA LUCERO

Full Stack Developer

CONTACT

■ shannaCodes@icloud.com

② Camarillo, CA, USA

linkedin.com/in/shannalucero

EDUCATION

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp

May 2023 - October 2023 Certificate in Full Stack Web & Mobile App Development

Cal State Dominguez Hills

M.S. Occupational Therapy

Cal State Long Beach

B.S. Business Administration,
Management Information Systems

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB
- Express
- React
- Node
- SQL
- Google Cloud

PROFILE

Mission-driven full stack developer with 10+ years of previous experience in the healthcare and therapy industry as a clinician, leader, and mentor. I aim to solve problems and enjoy the process. My ideal role will allow me to collaborate within a forward-thinking team, contribute to exciting projects, and grow within a supportive environment.

PROJECTS

Hand Exercise App

CRUD app to make custom hand and arm exercises for rehab professionals to share with other clinicians and their clients

- Skills: React, HTML, CSS, Express, Node, & MongoDB
- Challenges:
 - My app faced database access problems with MongoDB Compass and I was able to troubleshoot a solution by reading official documentation, managing the terminal, & manually coding permission for access
- What's Next?: I intend to add photo/video upload options for the exercises and allow users to select multiple exercises to make an exercise program
- Github: github.com/shannacodes/handtherapy-ex
- Live Page: hand-ex.web.app/

Rolling Pin Donuts Website

Revamped a popular local donut shop's web presence to a more modern, user-friendly and responsive experience

- Skills: Bootstrap, Javascript, HTML, & CSS
- Challenges:
 - The menu was quite vast, so I broke it down into smaller chunks of info for ease of user viewing using collapsible component features
- Github: github.com/shannacodes/bootstrapSite
- Live Page: rolling-pin-donuts.web.app/

SHANNA LUCERO

Full Stack Developer

SOFT SKILLS

- Personable
- Adaptable
- Reliabile
- Optimistic
- Embraces growth
- Attentive listener
- Transparent communicator
- Receptive to constructive feedback
- Values camaraderie and collaboration

VOLUNTEER WORK

Maker Space Volunteer

Pleasant Valley School District 2022 - present

Helped kindergarteners and 1st graders learn STEM concepts through a variety of kid-friendly hands-on labs

FUN FACTS

- I play the acoustic guitar and ukelele
- I enjoy DIY home decor
- I'm a big Star Wars fan
- I love to travel

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR HAND THERAPIST & OCCUPATIONAL THERAPIST (PREVIOUS CO-OWNER)

Hand Rehabilitation Specialists

September 2016 - Present

- Assisted in meeting weekly clinical KPI of >200 total patient visits total per week with 85% success rate
- Produced comprehensive data reports and performed in-depth analysis facilitating strategic business decision-making; key focus areas encompassed referral sources, insurance/payor data, account payable/receivable, and detailed expense reports
- Led a team of junior therapists by providing one-onone mentorship sessions and guidance through their professional growth within a culture of open communication, constructive feedback, and support
- Established processes and procedures to enhance the supplies ordering and receiving process using Cloudbased monitoring and tracking
- Deployed marketing tools to boost patient acquisition by developing SEO-centric social media content, crafting engaging blog posts, and conducting targeted webinars for specific niches
- Provided individualized patient care for people across the lifespan with various hand and upper arm injuries

IT IMPLEMENTATION INTERN Alcoa Fastening Systems

June 2008 - June 2009

- Provided end user training on Oracle purchasing processes through classroom-led and one-on-one training sessions
- Prepared technical training documentation, including user instructions and video tutorials
- Developed comprehensive User Acceptance Testing (UAT) test scripts outlining clear instructions and expected results